[
    {
        "question": "The ship ............ helped each other to control the situation well.",
        "choices": [
            "gang",
            "crew",
            "staff",
            "team"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "crew"
    },
    {
        "question": "The police found a ............ that helped them solve the crime.",
        "choices": [
            "glue",
            "True",
            "clue",
            "flu"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "clue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unfortunately, the burglar ............ the house.",
        "choices": [
            "stole",
            "took",
            "robbed",
            "guarded"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "robbed"
    },
    {
        "question": "A ............ is the most important person in an organization.",
        "choices": [
            "head",
            "crew",
            "clerk",
            "cleaner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "head"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is someone whose job is to live in another person's house and do jobs for them, such as cleaning.",
        "choices": [
            "magistrate",
            "officer",
            "servant",
            "interviewer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "servant"
    },
    {
        "question": "To ............ is to succeed in leaving a place when someone or something is trying to stop you.",
        "choices": [
            "rob",
            "escape",
            "guard",
            "dare"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "escape"
    },
    {
        "question": "A ............ is someone who decides if a person is guilty of less serious crimes in a court.",
        "choices": [
            "doctor",
            "sailor",
            "cook",
            "magistrate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "magistrate"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ is a group of valuable things such as gold, silver, jewels, etc.",
        "choices": [
            "Treasure",
            "Scar",
            "Adventure",
            "Head"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Treasure"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is a piece of land completely surrounded by water.",
        "choices": [
            "beach",
            "island",
            "desert",
            "inn"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "island"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is the mark (x or +) used on paper, to represent where something is, or where something should be.",
        "choices": [
            "equal",
            "plus",
            "cross",
            "minus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "cross"
    }
]